hair-styles.org 2002-06-02

# America's Hair On Line Media Company - Privacy Statement

**Our Privacy Policy**

L90, Inc., DoubleClick,  HAIROL and its sites, ARE deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. This Privacy Statement presents our privacy policy, including L90's privacy practices for our www.hair-news.com Web site. Below is information regarding L90's and DoubleClick's commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

 **

Third Party Advertising - DoubleClick

**

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here < _[ _http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)_ >

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Consumer Information - L90**  

In the course of delivering an ad to you, L90 does not collect personally identifiable information about you. In other words, we do not collect information, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. However, L90 does collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), the server your computer is logged into, the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for instance) and whether you responded to the ad delivered. 

This non-personally identifiable information that we collect is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring the effectiveness of ads on behalf of L90's advertisers and Web publishers. For more information on the types of non-personally identifiable information that is collected by L90, please **[click here](http://www.l90.com/external_site/privacy_collects.html)**. 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad. For instance, you may provide your address or email address in order to receive a catalogue. L90 may collect this information on behalf of the advertiser, who, in turn, will use this information to respond to your request for a catalogue. In addition, there may be instances in which you voluntarily elect to provide information in exchange for sweepstakes opportunities, special offers, promotions and other targeted offers based upon your interests. 

**Cookies and Opt Out**

Like most Internet sites, L90 uses "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. L90 cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files. 

What are cookies and how do they enhance your Web experience? 

A cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time L90 serves you an ad. This number is stored in a file on your computer and helps us target ads to you. For instance, cookies help L90 ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an ad. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested. 

Although we believe that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web (by not repeatedly serving the same ads to you and delivering more relevant messages to you), L90 does not need cookies to deliver ads to you. 

**Opt Out**

If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may either manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser, or you may **[click here](http://www.l90.com/external_site/privacy_optout.html)**.

**Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy**

L90 is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, including those established by the Direct Marketing Association. Furthermore, L90 is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. To review information regarding privacy practices on our L90 Web site, please **[click here](http://www.l90.com/external_site/privacy_policyL90.html)**. If you should have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact our Customer Services at **[customerservice@L90.com](mailto:customerservice@L90.com)**. We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Statement, as L90 may update it from time to time.

Sincerely:

HAIROL
